The world.
What a glorious place.
Seek freedom, and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit,
seize it, raise your flag, and stand tall.
I think back to the time
when my search first began.
I left behind those shores of sand.
For the endless everlasting
world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion having me.
Someday, somewhere, I'll finally see the
light I have searched for everywhere.
When the summer sun is shining.
Shaking the sails of my heart. I know.
A brand new world that has been hiding.
Has opened up its doors for me to go.
A wave on the blue sky.
Wearing in the troubled waves.
With more despair I can be saved.
For the horizon on the other side is.
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began.
Over streets of green and shores of sand.
Through the endless
everlasting world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me.
Someday somewhere I'll finally see the
light I will search for everywhere.
You boys had better catch her pretty soon.
She's getting away.
He's right you guys.
We need to get moving now.
Before we lose sight of her.
If we lose her in this forest.
Finding her again could be impossible.
Usopp, wait.
Finding each other won't be easy either.
Luffy, you coming?
You two go on ahead without me I'm
going to take care of Ball Guy.
Ha ha!
This should be amusing.
Do you really think you
can beat me, Rubber Boy?
Ha ha ha!
I guess someone needs to deal
with this pot-bellied freak.
Don't do anything reckless.
He has weird powers.
Back as soon as we get the boat.
Great.
It's just you and me now, fatso.
He'll grab that branch.
Eh, Gum-Gum!
Same move as before.
Pisto!
Oh, good.
Looks like this one will
be sticking around a while.
Now, where do those others scamper off to?
I'd be all so disappointed
if they got away.
Hmm.
There we are.
Hey, Usopp, you see it yet?
There she is!
Want to tell me where?
Straight ahead!
Climb up the one, two,
third tree on the right!
You can jump on when
she passes beneath you!
Gotcha!
Oh, crap!
It's that priest!
What's he doing?
Heads up, Sanji!
Killer ball coming your way!
What?
What's Luffy doing back there?
Surprise cloud billyards!
Usa!
That fat freak was aiming for me!
At least I died like a man.
What?
A flower?
It was a dud.
Bastard!
All right, you, that does it!
Now you made me mad!
Gum-gum-gattling!
Luffy, stop!
Use your head, you're
only making things worse!
Huh?
What the...
what the...
No! Oh, no!
It's too late!
Take cover!
They're coming at us from all sides!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Have fun, boys, I'll be watching!
Ah!
Yeah!
Woo-hoo!
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Spears! Crab!
Not for at once!
What the...
another dud?
I went straight through.
Luffy, you gotta catch yourself.
None of these rivers have a bottom.
Aaaaah!
Ah!
Too much!
Aaaaah!
Aaaaah! Ha-ha!
Will you get serious?
Usopp Hammer!
Ever been a doom?
Oh yeah, that reminds me.
I should try out my new thingy.
What's up, Usopp? You got an idea?
Do I?
Friend, they don't call me Usopp, the
technological pirate wizard for nothing.
Behold, my latest invention!
Usopp!
Yeah, what?
Just watch.
There's the crow.
Milky Road, straight ahead.
Perfect.
Here we go. Mine out!
Now what are they up to?
Yes, now I just have to swing
over there and catch the crow.
But my timing's got to
be absolutely perfect.
If I miss it, that's it.
We've only got one shot at this.
Not bad, but how are you going
to get past those spheres?
Just let me worry about that.
Did I happen to mention they
also call me king of the jungle?
Here goes.
Usopp!
Damn it!
Just jump!
Yeah, um, about that,
just one small problem.
I forgot the rope is sort
of attached to the belt.
I never really got around
to fixing that part.
Throw me some scissors or something.
Ah!
Garp, Garp, Garp, Garp!
Ah ha ha ha!
You two! Hey, Yusuf! What do you think?
This is a lot of fun, isn't it?
Ha ha ha!
I think I need to have a
little word with those two.
Here's the deal.
I'm going to forget about what just
happened, but now you do what I say.
Roy, I'm sorry. Yeah,
me too. What he said.
Okay, then.
First thing, we're going to
forget about the boat for now.
Then we're going to all
charge that fat freak at once.
I don't care what kind of powers he's got.
With all three of us
attacking at the same time,
if there's a way to
beat him, we'll find it.
Oh, don't be so sure.
Where did he go?
Impact!
Sanji!
Ha ha ha!
Like they say, life is pain!
Now, who wants to go next?
There good I'm sure glad
this thing was still here
fine tell you what just to
be safe I'll hold on to the
whistle any objections what
is with you people come on
I'm clearly the weakest one
here I need it more than you do
but but nothing it's the
only thing that makes sense
I want to blow it no forget
it bloofy if we give it to
you you're just gonna waste
it it's not a toy oh come
on I want to call Are you
still that weird old guy again?
No, let me have it.
I'm the weakest one here.
I should hold it.
You wish!
I'm the weakest and you all know it!
Oh, please!
How can you say that?
I'm just a poor defenseless girl! No way!
I'm weakest and I'm smallest! Hey!
I can be pretty damn helpless
when I put my mind to it!
No, Finn! Not my fault!
Fighting over who's most pathetic.
Odd.
Okay, here's how we're gonna do this.
Center of the ship,
we leave the whistle on the main mast
here, so if any of us gets into trouble,
all we have to do is run
over here and blow it.
Now it's fair to everyone. Fine. Okay.
And last thing, none of you are allowed
to blow it under any circumstances.
Got it?
Aw, can't I just call him one time?
You touch this whistle, and you'll
be swimming with the skyfish.
Fine, we got it.
Now if anything really bad happens,
the Sky Knight will come save me.
But I can only blow it as a last resort
Hear that?
Anyone wants to take this ship?
They have to get through me first!
What's that?
Just one?
Surely you're not the only
sacrifice I get to kill.
I'm referring to the pumpkins.
I don't think I've ever
grown them quite as sweet.
Of course.
I'm sorry, but my mind
is wandering elsewhere.
It's very kind of you to take us in.
I dislike putting you in this position.
Not at all.
If they believe that your daughter
let the Straw Hats escape,
they'll consider you an accomplice.
The only safe place for you is here.
You can consider this one on the house.
We're all lucky that Aniru's
mantra doesn't reach this far.
How are things back on the island?
I'm sorry, the crops are they
coming in hardy this year?
From what I know of it,
yes, quite well indeed.
Well, that's good to hear.
I prepared us some pumpkin juice,
made from the very ones
that grow here in my field.
Wonderful flavor.
Try some.
Thank you.
It looks refreshing.
Conis, dear, you should try this.
Young lady,
I'm curious if you've ever heard tale of
those from the Blue Sea
World called pirates.
Never.
They are basically just criminals
who travel on the water.
And though each ship may vary somewhat,
these pirates are usually recognized by
their flag with a skull
and crossbones on it.
I have my suspicions that your new
friends fall in line with this kind?
That's absurd!
You mean that these people were criminals
before they set foot on our shore?
They may not live by the
rules of their world,
but I can't necessarily call
that criminal There are those
who fall out of grace with the
rule of law in any society.
I don't see you two as
any different from them.
Who says that those who don't fit
in are wrong and others are right?
Sometimes the way of the world
is backwards and blurred,
and it can change in an instant.
For example, you kill a man in
war and you're branded a hero.
Kill the same man in peacetime and
you're prosecuted as a murderer.
I myself had a pirate
friend a long time ago.
He came here with his band more than 20
years ago while I was
still God of Skype here!
They were funny all of them.
Mistress people with lots to laugh
about and a general air of freedom.
I hated to say goodbye
The beauty of this land
masks a truth as old as time.
Skype is entangled in endless war!
We the people of the sky wage this
battle with those we call gorillas.
the Shandians.
Even now, they move against Eneru
constantly, trying to siege the sky.
I worry for all those I could not protect.
When you were God, you did
all that you could to coexist.
Even the Shandians were convinced of this.
You gave all of us hope that the several
hundred-year war would
end and leave us with
lasting peace.
I didn't have near enough time.
Eneru dethroned me before
I could solidify the
A treaty.
Wasted efforts.
I'm sorry for failing my people.
Stop that.
You have nothing to apologize for.
A legend is passed down through the
generations in Skypiea about its beginnings.
It is said that the day the Upper
Yard, the Sacred Grounds, was created,
the voice of the island sung forth a
beautiful song that echoed through the skies.
It was after that moment
that the tragedy between
the people of the sky
and the Shandians began.
As if on cue.
And so the legend says when we next
hear the singing voice of the island,
this war will finally come to an end.
The voice.
That's right.
And our sacred land
will sing again someday.
Someday.
Someday, she must.
Huh?
Is something happening?
Nothing you need worry about.
I've got a job to do.
You'll be safe here!
He's right!
This pumpkin juice is fantastic!
Yes, he's quite good
at cultivating things.
Not the mast!
Stop it, please!
Just stop burning the ship!
I'm serious, I don't want to die!
This is gonna hurt!
Oh, no.
If you want me, that's fine.
But you can't have the ship.
They put me in charge of it,
and I'm not letting them down.
So you back off now, mister.
What do you think we should do, Vice?
He's so impassioned.
He doesn't want us to
hurt any of his friends.
He's begging us not to torch his ship!
And he says, of course,
that he doesn't want to die.
I'm at a loss here?
You're a greedy little
hairball, aren't you?
And you get under my skin?
It's gone, Fall!
Why don't you try putting up a fight?
Your spear!
It's burning through the metal!
Why is he burning everything?
You creep!
Are you trying to survive this without
sacrificing anything of yourself?
There's more to this guy
than he's showing me.
He's not just a fighter.
It's like he can predict all of my moves.
For one to live, another must die.
That is the way of the world.
This is a sacrificial altar.
What did you think was going
to happen by you being up here?
I was supposed to fix the ship and
wait until my crewmates came back.
Be assured your friends are trying
their hardest to get back here.
Of course they're going to
find it incredibly difficult.
On this island there are four areas,
each of which is governed
by a different priest.
Our first rule is that when
the targets are in one area,
the other priests are not supposed
to interfere with them in any way.
But this sacrificial altar doesn't sit
inside the perimeter of any of the areas.
Here, we are in a freeze zone,
which means that any one of us
can attack those we find here.
And proper etiquette would
not have those at the altar
killed until after the targets
fail at a challenge and die.
What?!
Luffy and the others are dead?!
Calm yourself.
The fact that I am here
does not necessarily
mean your friends are dead at this point.
It's unfortunate, but true.
I stand before you now with a
different purpose than sacrifice.
What's different about it?
Wait,
you mean if my friends get
back here and rescue me,
then we're free to go, but you
won't let that happen, will you?
Well, that depends on you.
And whether you and your crew can make
your escape from the Free Zone fast enough.
What?
But hold that thought.
The reason I'm here is because those are
the judgment rules under normal conditions.
However,
when there is an exceptional situation,
the rules are set to change a little.
Exceptional?
Yes. Exceptional.
Say, for example,
three sacrifices were to escape the altar
and swing to the main island using vines.
Oh, that kind of situation.
I say we should cross over and see
what's on the other side of the river.
It's all hateful!
Someone has to lose their life to bring
balance back after your friend's escape.
It's atonement, and
sacrifice is part of life.
I want them to see it when they come back.
Their good friend lying on
deck, the life drained from him.
Then they will realize the
severity of their mistakes.
And now, I offer your life to God!
No!
Now die.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's Gonfall, the skylight!
I wasn't expecting company.
Gonfall!
I knew you wouldn't let me down, skylight!
We're not dealing with
an amateur here, Pierre.
I wouldn't want to disappoint a worthy
opponent with anything but our best
What could that decrepit old
relic possibly be doing here?
Do you feel like putting him in his place?
Enough stalling we don't
need two gods on this island
Oh, my God.
Skye Knight, you're my hero! Help!
One more hit in the right spot should
do it for him, eh, Pierre? Yeah!
I've had enough!
You're nothing but a pathetic
shell of your former self.
And I'm through playing games with a fool!
You showed up to this fight a criminal.
Which leaves me only one option.
Take you out.
Ordeal of string!
Ah-hoo!
You're still alive!
I'm impressed!
And as a reward for good behavior,
we're going to finish our little fun today
with a move I've received
several awards for. Ah-hoo!
My super-secret surprise!
Where have you been, child?
Come a kitty!
The upper yard again, right?
And that's probably Fourth in your bag.
Stay away from that place, Isa.
Or you will die.
Nah!
You can't tell me what to do!
You haven't even been
able to beat Inaru yet!
What a brat.
What?
An opportunity? That's right.
For some reason, Gonfall
entered the upper yard,
which of course drew the
attention of the priests.
You see,
that old bag of bones thinks it's his
responsibility to protect
the people of Skypiea.
And that will only make him weak.
We would be wise to strike while our
enemies are occupied with each other.
The great warrior Kalgaras said,
light the fire of Shandora.
Our people will do just that.
No one can deny us our destiny,
be it Gonfall or Eneru, and
now is the time to take action!
They have had the audacity to reign
as god, and that is unforgivable!
No matter how different from
one another they may seem,
I assure you they are the same,
and they must be eliminated.
Wiper,
it has been six years
since Inneru began his
reign and for the first
time since he took power.
A rebel has appeared on Angel Island.
A young woman. I hear.
Get to the point, Locky.
Because the Sky Knight rescued
the young rebel from judgment.
Inneru now has reason to
directly confront Gonfall.
In order to judge him,
a battle like this between the former
god and the current god has never?
happened, strategically this
could be most advantageous to us.
We must remember that Gonfall
has never harmed any of us.
Not as the Sky Knight, and
not during his reign as God.
The fact that he never
hurt any of us doesn't
change that he ruled with
absolute authority as God.
And although he is our enemy's enemy,
that does not make him our ally.
If he and one of the priests
kill each other in battle,
that will serve our purposes just fine.
Otherwise, he is of no use to us.
If you have any doubts at all
about this fight, stay out.
You'll just be in the way.
Ice.
Upper Yard?
What Upper Yard?
I didn't go to Upper Yard,
I promise you I didn't!
You can't go into the tent yet.
Wiper descendant of the great
warrior Kokoro is angry right now.
Careful.
Oh he's scary when he gets mad.
Scarier than God.
Help them?
Us?
How Conis?
My dear child?
It's only right.
that you and I should try to
create some way for them to escape.
Wow, I can't believe how fast they are.
Awesome.
I can see that diplomacy is
no longer an option for me.
Diplomacy is for the weak!
This battle is intense.
Heaven's judgment!
That young woman did something foolish.
She brought this upon us.
She knows we're not supposed to anger him.
Please come back to us, God.
You're mine.
Is something wrong, Gonfall?
Shura, what have you done?
Why can't we move?
You old fool.
Time to die.
Mysterious, the strings are.
If you have the audacity to enter Upper
Yard, you must answer to the four priests.
You were foolish to
think you could beat us.
He's falling! Oh no!
God Enuru is glorious.
Perfect, and far beyond your reach.
and our sacred land will sing
again someday someday she must
Second!